These were expensive
and he'll grow out of them...
아주 비싼데다
금방 못 신게 되겠지만
...in 20 minutes,
but I couldn't resist!
지나칠 수가 없었어!
Look at these.
너무 귀여워!
신어 봐, 'Just do it'!
Hey, Ben.
"Just do it"!
이걸 어째...
너무 부담 줬나?
Oh, my God!
Was that too much
pressure for him?
-ls he hungry already?
-I guess so.
- 벌써 쭈쭈가 먹고 싶나?
- 그런가 봐
사실...
You know, it's....
아기들한테는 역시 운동화야
금방 올게
Something funny about sneakers.
I'll be right back.
나도 하나 살래
I gotta get one too.
뭣들 해?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
수저 옆에서 놀잖아
We're just hanging out
by the spoons.
Ladle?
국자 줄까?
Will you guys grow up?
둘 다 철 좀 들어
얼마나 아름다운 건데
This is the most beautiful
thing in the world.
알아, 하지만 아기가 빨잖아
Yeah, we know.
But there's a baby sucking on it.
This is my son having lunch, okay?
It'll happen a lot, so get used to it.
내 아들이 점심을 먹는
모습이야, 알겠어?
앞으로 자주 볼 텐데
익숙해지라고
그래도 불편하면
무엇이든 물어 보라고
If you're uncomfortable,
just ask questions.
캐롤은 괜찮으니까
어서 이리 와
Carol's fine with it.
Carol?
캐롤?
I'm wondering, could Joey ask you
a question about breast-feeding?
조이가 모유 수유에 대해
질문해도 괜찮을까요?
그럼요
Sure.
Does it hurt?
아파요?
처음엔 좀 아팠는데
이제 괜찮아요
It did at first, but not anymore.
챈들러?
Chandler?
얼마나 자주 먹일 수 있죠?
So, how often can you do it?
아기가 배고플 때마다
As much as he needs.
나 질문 생겼어
Okay, I got one, I got one.
아기가 한쪽을 불면
다른 쪽이 커지나요?
If he blows into one,
does the other one get bigger?
The One With the Breast Milk
- 빵 남은 거 없어요?
- 어떤 빵이랬죠?
-Any muffins left?
-Yeah, I forget which ones.
You're busy, I'll get it.
바쁘면 내가 가져올게요
- 누구 먹을 사람?
- 괜찮아요
-Anyone else want one?
-No, thanks.
You're losing your apron.
Let me get it.
앞치마가 흘러내리네
묶어 줄게요
-There you go.
-Thank you.
- 됐어요
- 고마워요
What a bitch!
요망한 것!
백화점에서 일하는 내 친구가
내일 폐업 할인을 하는데
I have a friend at
Bloomingdale's who's quitting...
...and he wants to abuse his discount.
가고 싶은 사람 있어요?
Anyone want to come
take advantage of it?
난 안 돼요, 할머니와
가축병원에 가거든요
I have to take
my grandmother to the vet.
- 그럼 나랑 같이 가요
- 좋아요
-I'll go with you.
-Great.
-Hi, honey.
-Hey, sweetums.
- 안녕, 자기
- 안녕, 예쁜이
And hello to the rest.
- 나머지도 안녕?
- 어서 와
너 정신 나갔어?
You can't go shopping with her.
What about Rachel?
줄리랑 쇼핑을 가다니
레이첼은 어쩌고?
문제가 되겠지?
Will it be a problem?
You're going to
Bloomingdale's with Julie.
줄리와 쇼핑을 가는 건
It's like cheating on Rachel
in her house of worship.
레이첼 눈앞에서
바람피우는 격이라고!
- 하지만...
- 널 죽일지도 몰라
Monica, she will kill you.
집 잃은 미친개처럼 말야
She will kill you
like a dog in the street!
So Jules tells me you guys
are going shopping tomorrow.
줄리랑 내일 쇼핑간다며?
별일도 아닌데 뭘
It's actually not that big a deal.
내겐 중대한 일이야
잘 생각했어, 고마워
It's a big deal to me.
This is great.
I really appreciate this.
You're welcome.
천만에
Bijan for men?
'비잔' 써 보세요
'비잔' 쓰세요
Bijan for men?
-Hey, Annabel.
-Hey, Joey.
- 애나벨!
- 안녕, 조이
Did you hear about the new guy?
신참에 대해 들었어?
- 누구?
- 이름은 아무도 몰라
Nobody knows his name. Me and
the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
여자들끼린 그냥
'옴브레맨'으로 통해
Hombre?
옴브레!
What's he doing in my section?
왜 내 구역에서 저래?
I guess he doesn't know.
- 상관 안 할걸
- 그럼 내가 상관하지
Well, he's gonna.
I'll see you a little later, okay?
나중에 보자고
Hey, how you doing?
안녕하셔?
Mornin'.
좋은 아침
Listen, I know you're new...
신참인 건 알겠지만
신사복 코너에서
에스컬레이터까지는
... but it's understood
that everything...
...from young men's to
the escalator is my territory.
내 구역이거든
"Your territory"?
- 네 구역?
- 그래
-Bijan for men?
-No, thanks.
- '비잔' 쓰세요
- 됐수
Hombre?
- 옴브레?
- 좋죠
Yeah, all right.
You were saying?
봤지?
Phoebe, listen. You were with me,
and we were shopping all day.
피비, 잘 들어
우리 둘이 쇼핑한 거야
뭐?
We shopped and we had lunch.
오늘 우리 둘이서 쇼핑하고
점심 먹었다고
What did I have?
내가 뭐 먹었는데?
-You had a salad.
-No wonder I don't feel full.
- 샐러드
- 그래서 배가 고팠구나
Hi. What's up?
잘 있었니?
I went shopping with Monica
and I had a salad.
나 모니카랑 종일 쇼핑하고
샐러드 먹었어
Good, Pheebs.
What'd you buy?
재밌었겠네, 피비
뭘 샀는데?
쇼핑하러 가서...
We went shopping for....
산 게... 산 게...
For....
For fur.
'산 게' 샀어
You went shopping for fur?
- 산 게를 사?
- 그래
And then I realized
that l'm against that.
한데 난 그거 싫어하잖니
그래서 대신...
So then we bought some....
젖을 샀지
Boobs.
You bought boobs?
젖을 샀다고?
Bras!
맞아, 브래지어!
브래지어 샀어!
We bought bras!
We bought bras.
우린 브래지어 샀어
'비잔'입니다
Bijan for men?
'비잔' 쓰세요
Bijan for....
'비잔'...
애나벨!
Hey, Annabel.
I was wondering if after work
we could grab a cup of coffee?
퇴근하고 커피 할래?
Actually, I sort of have plans.
미안, 선약이 있거든
갈까, 애나벨?
You ready, Annabel?
You bet.
좋아요
Maybe some other time.
- 나중에 마시자
- 그래
It's not the first time I lost a girl
to a cowboy spraying cologne.
전에도 향수 뿌리는
카우보이에게 여자 빼앗겼죠
Bijan for men?
'비잔'입니다
Bijan for men!
한번 써 봐요!
And this is Funny Clown.
이 광대인형은
낮잠을 자고 나면 줘
It's only for after his naps,
not before, or he won't sleep.
그 전에 주면 안 자거든
We've been through this before.
We have a good time.
처음 아기 보는 것도
아니잖아
함께 웃고 놀고...
아버지와 아들처럼
We laugh, we play.
It's like we're father and son.
걱정하지 마
로스는 애 잘 본다고
Honey, relax.
Ross is great with him.
Don't look so surprised.
I'm a lovely person.
그렇게 쳐다보지 마
난 원래 예쁘니까
너무 앙증맞아!
This is so cute!
내가 샀어요!
I got that for him!
'우리 엄마들은 날 사랑해요'
"My Mommies Love Me. "
That's clever.
머리 썼군요
여보세요?
안녕하세요, 줄...
Oh, hi, Jul....
Hi, Jew!
안녕, 주여!
Okay, sure.
좋아요
그럼 그 때 봐요
That'd be great.
See you then. Bye.
Did you just say, " Hi, Jew"?
방금 '주여'라고 했어?
응, 그랬어
Yes, I did.
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
에디 모스코위치라는 친구야
Yeah, he likes it.
Reaffirms his faith.
그렇게 불러 주면
신앙심이 살아 난다나
벤, 저녁 먹으렴
Ben, dinner!
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs.
고마워요, 피비 아줌마
Did you microwave that?
You can't do that to breast milk.
레인지에 데웠어?
모유는 그럼 안 되거든
모유도 못 데울까 봐서?
I think I know
how to heat breast milk.
됐어
지금 뭔 짓을 한 거야?
What did you just do?
I licked my arm, what?
내 팔 핥았잖아, 왜?
이건 모유야!
It's breast milk!
So?
그래서?
사람에게서 나온 분비물이잖아
Phoebe, that is juice
squeezed from a person.
웬 법석이야?
What is the big deal?
안 돼!
지금 뭔 짓이야?
What did you just do?
Can people stop
drinking the breast milk?
이제 애 젖 좀 그만 먹어!
You won't even taste it?
맛보는 것도 싫어?
싫어!
Not even if you just
pretend it's milk?
우유처럼 생각하면?
Not even if Carol's breast had
a picture of a missing child on it.
캐롤의 가슴이 우유병이라도
난 싫어
- 다들 어디 있어?
- 벤 데리고 공원에
-Where is everybody?
-At the park. Where have you been?
넌 어디 갔다 왔어?
Just out.
밖에서 점심 먹고 왔어
나 혼자서
Had some lunch. Just me.
A little quality time with me.
혼자만의 시간을 가졌지
- 재킷 잘 입었어
- 웬걸
-Thanks for your jacket.
-No problem.
You can borrow it, by the way.
다음부턴 빌려 달라고 해
Here are your keys, honey.
여기 네 열쇠
모니카?
혼자 점심을 먹었는데
53달러나 나왔어?
If you were at lunch alone,
how come it cost you $53?
You know what probably happened?
이렇게 됐을 거야
Someone stole my credit card.
누군가 내 신용카드를
훔쳐갔다고
And put the receipt
back in your pocket?
영수증은 주머니에 넣어 주고?
That is an excellent,
excellent question.
정말이지 좋은 지적이야
That is excellent.
정말 예리해
What's with you?
Who did you have lunch with?
누구랑 점심 먹었는데?
- 주디
- 누구?
-Judy.
-Who?
- 줄리
- 뭐라고?
-Julie.
-What?
조디!
Jody.
You were with Julie?
줄리를 만났어?
그게...
When it started, I was just
trying to be nice to her...
처음엔 오빠 애인이라서
잘해주려던 것뿐이었어
... because she was
my brother's girlfriend.
And then one thing
led to another...
한데 자꾸 만나게 되고
그러다 어느새...
...and before I knew it, we were...
...shopping.
쇼핑도 했어
Oh, my God!
주여!
Wait, we only did it once.
단 한 번이었어
It meant nothing to me!
내겐 아무 의미도 없었어
- 어련하겠어
- 정말이야!
쇼핑하면서도
네 생각만 했다고!
Really, I was thinking
of you the whole time.
Look, I'm sorry, all right?
I never meant for you to find out.
정말 미안해
네겐 숨기려고 했었어
Oh, please! Please!
You wanted to get caught!
변명 그만둬!
일부러 잡힌 거잖아!
That is not true!
그렇지 않아!
So you just happened
to leave it in here?
그럼 모르고 영수증을
주머니에 넣어뒀다고?
Did it ever occur to you
that I might just be that stupid?
내가 원래 멍청한 걸
몰랐단 말야?
Okay, I just have to know one thing.
딱 한 가지만 물을게
Did you go to Bloomingdale's?
둘이 백화점도 갔어?
어쩜!
좋아, 좋다고
Okay, I just really need
to not be with you right now.
지금은 혼자 있고 싶어
Hi, who's this?
누구세요?
Hi, Joanne. Is Rachel working?
It's Monica.
조앤, 레이첼 있어요?
저 모니카예요
Yes, I know I did a horrible thing.
못할 짓 한 거 알아요
Joanne, it's not
as simple as all that.
그리 간단하지 않아요
스티브가 뭐라든 상관없어요!
안녕, 스티브
No, I don't care what Steve thinks.
Hi, Steve.
어땠어요?
How did we do?
내가 벤 우유 맛봤다고
로스가 기겁했어요
I tasted Ben's milk
and Ross freaked out.
내가 뭘 기겁해?
I did not freak out.
-Why'd you freak out?
-Because it's breast milk.
- 왜 기겁했어?
- 모유니까...
It's gross!
역겹잖아
My breast milk is gross?
내 모유가 역겹다고?
This should be fun.
재밌어지는데
아니, 그런 뜻이 아니라
There's nothing wrong with it.
I just don't think
breast milk is for adults.
어른이 모유를 먹기엔
좀 그렇단 뜻이야
Of course, the packaging does
appeal to grownups and kids.
하긴 그래, 어른들은
겉포장을 더 좋아하잖아
Don't be silly. I've tried it.
It's no big deal.
나도 먹었는데 괜찮아
로스, 어서 먹어 봐
Just taste it.
이렇게 대답할게
싫어!
That would be no.
- 어서!
- 먹어 봐
-Come on.
-Try it.
- 자연식이잖아
- 싫어!
It's natural.
It doesn't taste bad.
맛도 나쁘지 않아
Yeah, it tastes kind of sweet.
Sort of like....
그래, 달짝지근해
뭐랄까...
Like what?
뭐처럼?
Cantaloupe juice.
- 메론 주스
- 맞아!
Exactly.
먹어 봤군
You've tasted it.
먹어 봤어?
그래
Oh, you've tasted it.
정말 먹어 봤어?
You can keep saying it,
but it won't stop being true.
몇 번을 물어 봐도
대답은 바뀌지 않아
병 가져와
Give me the bottle.
Get me the towel.
수건도 줘
안녕하신가?
Howdy.
주스 가져와
Give me a box of juice.
Well, they switched me over to Hombre.
날 '옴브레'로 보냈어
Maybe it's because of
the way you're dressed.
옷을 그렇게 입었으니까
Or this guy's doing so good
they want to put more people on it.
그 친구가 너무 잘해서
인원을 늘리는 거야
하루에 두 병이나
뿌려댄다고!
This guy goes through
two bottles a day now.
뭘 신경 써?
What do you care?
You're an actor.
This is your day job. It's nothing!
넌 배우야
이건 일종의 아르바이트고
I know, but I was the best.
그건 알지만
난 얼마 전까지 최고였어
난 최고인 게 좋다고
You know? I liked being the best.
Maybe I should get
out of the game.
향수 코너는 그만두고
가정용품 코너에서
치즈 시식이나 할까 봐
They need guys up in housewares
to serve cheese.
Say you do that.
나중에 치즈를 더 잘 써는
사람이 나타나면?
Sooner or later, somebody will come
along that slices a better cheddar.
Then where you gonna run?
그럼 어디로 도망갈 거지?
- 네 말이 옳아
- 그럼!
You're right.
I say you show him what you're made of.
Stand your ground.
그 친구에게 네 진가를
보여 주란 말이야
Show him that you're the baddest
Hombre west of the lingerie!
네가 얼마나 멋진 놈인지
그냥 한방 먹여버려!
-I'm gonna do it!
-All right!
- 하겠어!
- 좋아!
Now, go see Miss Kitty and
she'll fix you up with a nice hooker.
포주에게 가 봐
창녀 소개해 줄 테니까
I don't know what to say.
더 할말도 없어
그거 잘됐네
난 듣고 싶지 않거든
That's good because I'm not listening.
I feel terrible. I really do.
내 기분도 안 좋아
저런, 미안해라
내 등에 칼 찔렸어?
I'm sorry.
Did my back hurt your knife?
레이첼!
Say that I'm friends with her.
Is that so terrible?
함께 시간 좀 보낸 게
그렇게 잘못된 거야?
- 그래
- 그렇게 잘못됐어?
-It's that terrible?
-You don't get it!
그래, 모르겠니?
It's bad enough
she stole the guy...
내 천생배필일지 모르는
남자를 훔쳐간 여자야!
...who may be the person
l'm supposed to be with.
But now...
한데 이젠...
...she's actually....
그 여자가...
너까지 훔쳐가잖아!
But now she's actually stealing you!
나?
그런 말이 어딨어?
What are you talking about?
아무도 우리 사이를
갈라놓을 순 없어
Nobody could steal me from you.
Because I'm friends with her doesn't
make me any less friends with you.
내가 줄리랑 친구라고
너랑 의절하는 건 아냐
넌...
You're my....
And we're....
우리는...
-Oh, I love you!
-I love you too!
- 사랑해!
- 나도 사랑해!
You guys, I know that this really
doesn't have anything to do with me.
애들아...
난 상관없는 일이지만
나도 너희들 사랑해!
But I love you guys too!
이제 속이 후련하네
I really needed that.
I know that right now...
네가 줄리를 싫어하는
이유는 잘 알아
...you really need
to hate Julie's guts.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
하지만 줄리 잘못은 아냐
She's just a girl who met a guy,
and now they go out.
좋은 남자를 만난
여자일 뿐이라고
I think that if you gave her
a chance, you'd like her.
줄리에게 기회를 줘 봐
너도 좋아할 거야
Will you give it a chance?
그래 주겠어?
날 위해서
For me?
I'd do anything for you,
you know that.
널 위해선 못할 게 없어!
나도 그래!
I'd do anything for you!
잠깐, 잠깐!
Wait, wait, wait!
Mornin'.
굿모닝
I said, mornin'!
굿모닝이라고 했잖아
들었어
I heard you.
개장합니다!
All right, everybody.
I'm opening the doors.
You boys ready?
두 사람 준비됐어?
Ready.
준비됐어요
나도 준비 끝!
Yeah, l'm ready.
이 멍청한 카우보이!
You idiot! You stupid cowboy!
You've blinded me! I'm suing!
눈에다 뿌렸잖아!
고소하겠어!
맙소사!
토드, 왜 그랬어?
Oh, my God! Todd!
What the hell did you do?
Sorry. I'm such a doofus!
정말 죄송해요
제가 좀 멍청해서
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
My God, what happened?
무슨 일이야?
신참들은 오래 못 가거든
These new kids, they never last.
Sooner or later they all...
얼마 못 가서는...
죄 사라지고 말 거야
...stop lasting.
What do you say I buy you
that cup of coffee now?
우리 커피 마시러 갈까?
Sure.
좋아
- 그랬어요
- 네
I just thought we should hang out.
우리 친하게 지내요
I mean, you know,
we've never really talked.
우린 대화도 없었고
관련 당사자니까
잘 알겠지만요
I guess you'd know that,
being one of the two of us.
I know.
그래요
I probably shouldn't
even tell you this...
이런 말해도 될지...
... but l'm pretty much
totally intimidated by you.
사실 레이첼이 두려웠어요
정말로요?
내가 왜요?
Really?
Me?
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
몰라서 물어요?
Ross is so crazy about you...
로스는 레이첼을 좋아하고
난 친하게 지내고 싶은데
...and I really wanted you
to like me, and l....
It's probably me just
being totally paranoid...
내가 지레 겁먹어서겠지만
...but I kind of got the feeling
that maybe you don't.
레이첼은 그렇지 않다고
생각했거든요
괜한 걱정은 아니네요
Well, you're not totally paranoid.
좋아요
세상에나...
처음 둘을 보았을 때
나도 힘들었어요
When you and Ross
first started going out...
...it was really hard for me...
...for many reasons of which
l'm not gonna bore you with now.
이유야 많지만
지금 말하긴 그렇네요
로스는 행복하고
둘이 아주 잘 어울려요
I see how happy he is
and how good you guys are together.
And Monica's always
saying how nice you are...
모니카는 당신 칭찬이
대단해요
그런 모니카가
얄밉기는 하지만요
...and God, I hate it when she's right!
고마워요
Thanks.
언제 영화 보러 갈래요?
Would you like to go to
a movie sometime or something?
좋아요
재미있겠어요
Yeah, that'd be great.
I'd love it.
- 나도요
- 그래요
I'd love it too.
Shoot, I gotta go.
이런, 그만 가야겠어요
나중에 봐요
-So I'll talk to you later.
-All right, Julie.
- 그래요, 줄리
- 갈게요
요망한 것!
What a manipulative bitch.
생각보다 괜찮네
It's not bad.